{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n2x^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n2x^6 - 8x^5 + 14x^4 + 4x^2 + 14x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^4y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11x^4y^3 + 6x^3y^3 - 6x^2y^3 + 11xy^2 - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n10x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n10x^3y^2 + 4x^2y^2 + 12xy^2 - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x - 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^2y^2 - 8xy^2 + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^4y - 11x^3y^3 - 6x^2y^3 - 12xy^3 + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^6 + 3x^5 - 9x^4 + 12x^3 - 2x^2 + 2x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-12x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-12x^3y^2 + 10x^2y - 10xy^2 + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n4x^7y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^7y^3 + 15x^6y + 13x^5y - 11x^4y + 12x^3y + 10x^2y^2 - 13xy + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^7y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^7y^4 - 6x^6y^4 - 12x^5y^6 + 7x^3y^6 + 3x^2y^6 + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n2x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n2x^2 - 11x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x^6y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x^6y^2 + 6x^5y^2 + 15x^4y^2 - 8x^3y^2 - 10x^2y^2 + 9xy^2 - 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x^2 - 13x + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\nx^7y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\nx^7y^5 + 8x^6y^5 + 13x^5y^5 + 9x^4y^5 + 15x^3y^5 + 6x^2y^5 - 3xy^5 + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^4 + 7x^3 + 10x^2 - 7x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x^2 + 6x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n10x^4y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n10x^4y^4 - 11x^3y^4 + 10x^2y^4 + 9xy^4 + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-10x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-10x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n7xy\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n7xy + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n0\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^6y^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^6y^6 - 13x^5y^6 + 2x^4y^3 - 9x^3y^6 + 12x^2y^6 + 8xy^3 + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^5y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^5y^3 + 10x^4y^4 + 12x^3y^3 + 13x^2y^3 - 8xy^3 + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x^3y^2 + 12x^2y + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n12xy\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n12xy + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^6y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^6y^5 - x^5y^5 - 13x^4y^5 - 10x^3y^5 - 6x^2y^5 + 15xy^5 + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n15x^7y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n15x^7y^3 - 10x^4y^5 - 7x^3y^5 - 9x^2y^5 + 3xy^3 + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^4y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^4y^4 - 13x^3y - 6x^2y + xy + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2x^7y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2x^7y^3 - 8x^6y^3 - 12x^5y^3 + 8x^4y^3 - 4x^3y^3 + 6x^2y^3 - 7xy^3 - 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-3x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-3x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n6x^6y^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n6x^6y^6 - 5x^5y^6 - x^4y^6 + 11x^3y^6 - 4x^2y^6 - 4xy^6 + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n12x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n12x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^7y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x^7y^3 - x^5y^5 - 4x^4y^3 - 3x^3y^5 + 15x^2y^3 - 7xy^3 - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^4y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-4x^5y^2 + 8x^4y^4 + 2x^2y^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-7x^5y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-7x^5y^5 - 13x^4y^3 - 11x^3y^5 + 12x^2y^5 + 15xy^3 + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n10x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n10x^3 - 5x^2 - 11x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^7y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^7y^5 + 3x^6y^5 + 15x^4y^5 + 7x^3y^5 - 10x^2y^5 + 14xy^5 + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^6y^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^6y^6 + 14x^5y + 12x^4y - 11x^3y^6 + 9x^2y - 13xy^4 - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11x^3y^2 - 6x^2y^2 + 3xy^2 - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-8x^5y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-8x^5y + 10x^4y + 4x^3y^3 + 2x^2y + 9xy^3 + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^6y^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^6y^6 + 15x^5y^6 - 6x^4y^6 + 2x^3y^6 + 11x^2y^6 - 2x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n2x^6y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^7y^2 + 2x^6y^2 - 8x^5y^2 + 2x^4y^7 + 8x^3y^7 + 10x^2y^2 + 15x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-7x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-7x^2y^2 + 13xy^2 + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^6y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^6y^2 + x^4y^2 + 12x^3y^2 - 6x^2y^4 - 9xy^2 + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x^6y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x^6y^5 + 13x^4y^5 - 11x^3y^3 + x^2y^3 - 11xy^6 + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2x^3y^2 - 4x^2y^3 + 14xy - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x^3y^3 + 7x^2y^3 - 10xy^3 - 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-8x^5y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-8x^5y^5 + 14x^4y^5 - 7x^3y^5 + x^2y^5 + 13xy^5 - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-xy\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-xy + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^3y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^3y - 10x^2y - 13xy - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^3 - 10x^2 + 12x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-12x^4y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-12x^4y^2 + 7x^3y^3 + x^2y^2 + 4xy^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^5y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^5y - 13x^4y^2 + 11x^3y^2 - 13x^2y - 12xy^5 + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n5x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n5x^2 - 7x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-8x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-8x^3 - 11x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n4x^6y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^6y^4 + 3x^5y^5 - 9x^4y^4 - 6x^3y^4 - 12x^2y^4 + 2xy^4 - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2x^5y^4 + 12x^4y^5 - 13x^3y^5 + x^2y^5 - 13xy^5 + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n0\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n0", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^5y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^5y - x^4y - 2x^3y - 10x^2y + 13xy - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^7y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^7y^2 + 5x^6y^2 + 8x^4y^2 + 3x^3y^2 - 4x^2y^3 + 13xy^3 - 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n14x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n14x^5y^4 - 6x^3y^2 + 10x^2y^2 + 4xy^3 - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n5x^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n5x^5 + 6x^4 - 2x^3 + 4x^2 - 3x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n15x^4y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\nx^5y + 15x^4y^5 + 9x^3y + x^2y - 7xy + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n6x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n6x^5y^4 - 4x^4y^4 + 9x^3y^4 + 5xy^4 - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\nx^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\nx^2 + 9x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n13x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n13x^2y^2 - 7xy^2 - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-3x^5y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-3x^5y^2 - 13x^4y^2 - 7x^3y^2 + 6x^2y^2 - 12xy^2 - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11xy^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11xy^2 + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^3y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^3y - 11x^2y^2 - 7xy - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^6y^7\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n7x^7y^4 - 3x^6y^7 - 9x^5y^7 + 13x^4y^7 - 6x^3y^7 - x^2y^7 + xy^7 - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^2y^2 - xy^2 - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^4y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11x^4y - 8x^3y^2 - 11x^2y^2 - 11xy^3 - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^5y^4 + 13x^4y^3 + 3x^3y^3 - 6x^2y^3 + 10xy^3 + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^2 + 14x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^5y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x^5y^5 - 9x^4y^5 + 6x^3y^5 + 6x^2y^4 - 11xy^4 + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n4x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^2 + 9x + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n5x^3y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n12x^4y^2 + 5x^3y^4 - 9x^2y^2 + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n15x^7y^7\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n15x^7y^7 - 13x^6y^4 - 9x^5y^7 + 14x^4y^4 + 5x^3y^7 - 9x^2y^7 - 7xy^7 + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11x^3y^3 + 7x^2y^3 - 10xy^2 - 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-3x^7y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-3x^7y^4 + 2x^6y^4 + x^5y^4 + 10x^4y^4 + 13x^3y^4 + 6x^2y^4 + 4xy^4 + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^5y^4 + 2x^4y^4 - 11x^3y^4 - 11x^2y^4 + 11xy^4 + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^4y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^4y + 12x^3y + 13x^2y^2 + 10xy + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^2y^2 - 12xy^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^3y^2 + 2x^2y^2 - 7xy^2 + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^7y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^7y^2 + 5x^6y^2 + 6x^5y^2 + 15x^4y^2 - 6x^3y^2 + 5x^2y^2 + 9xy^2 - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n15x^5y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n15x^5y - 13x^4y + 13x^3y^3 + 7x^2y + 7xy + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n2x^5y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n2x^5y^5 - 5x^4y^5 + 3x^3y^5 - 6x^2y^5 - 2xy^5 - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\nx^7y^7\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\nx^7y^7 + 4x^6y^3 + 5x^5y^6 - 10x^4y^6 - 9x^3y^3 + 13x^2y^6 + 11xy^3 + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n14x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n14x^2y^2 - 5xy^2 + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2xy^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2xy^2 + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x^4 + 6x^3 - 8x^2 - 10x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n4x^4y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^4y - 2x^3y - 13xy - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n15x^2y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n15x^2y + 11xy - 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^5y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^6y^2 + 9x^5y^2 - 7x^4y^6 - 9x^3y^2 - 9x^2y^5 + 2xy^4 + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\nxy\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\nxy + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^4y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^4y^3 - 5x^3y^3 - 5x^2y^3 + 3xy^3 + 10", "type": "text"}
]}